EBI DANIEL CHUKWUEBUKA

ebidaniel427@gmail.com | | +234 8131930371 or 09029546537 | | Lagos, Nigeria

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Graduate of Computer Science and Statistics with years of experience as a frontend web developer. My passion and zeal in tech related skills motivates me to learn new ways of being a problem-solver with the help of programming, in the case web development alongside my proficient skills in HTML, CSS (BOOTSTRAP, MATERIAL-UI, TAILWIND), JAVASCRIPT (REACT, NEXT, TYPESCRIPT, NODE, EXPRESS, MONGODB), PLAYWRIGHT (FOR END-TO-END TESTING).

SKILLS

- Keen eye for building responsive websites
- Good knowledge of OOP and Networking
- Proficient in software and hardware maintenance
- MS-Office, MS-Excel, MS-PowerPoint
- Excellent Communication skills
- Ability to adapt to new technologies
- Good UI/UX development skills

- Good knowledge of GIT and GITHUB
- Result oriented and critical thinking ability to aid good decision making
- Sound knowledge of database (MongoDB)
- Ability to work with a team.
- Good time management skills

WORK HISTORY

Nov 2022 Till Date ICT Admin, Lin-Daves College, Amuwo-odofin, Lagos.

- Managed the ICT laboratory for smooth operations.
- Troubleshooting of PC's in the laboratory
- Installing of software and maintaining the hardware
- Managed schools data backups
- Designing flyer and logos
- Preparing soft copy of result sheet and newsletters

Oct 2022 Till Date Coding Coach CodeJika, South Africa.

- Teaching teens in schools how to code, starting with the basics of web development technologies.
- Creating coding clubs and coding activities for the students.
- Troubleshooting their computer and setting them up for optimal performance.

Apr 2015 - Mar 2016
ICT Consultant team
Noben Printing Press
Onitsha, Anambra State,

- Installing and updating of softwares
- Replacing damaged hardwares
- Networking the computers and setting up internet access
- Installing new printers

EDUCATION

02/2022

Bachelor of Technology: Statistics | Federal University of Technology | Owerri

08/2015

Ordinary National Diploma: Computer Science | Federal Polytechnic Nekede | Owerri

09/2009

West Africans Examination Council WASSCE/O Level

Christ the King College Onitsha | Anambra state

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Workshop on Statistical Packages (Rida Planet) 2019
- Frontend web developer (hub.Applinet.com.ng)
- Certified React intermediate web dev (KodeCamp)
- Intern at KodeHauz (currently)
- Certified Data Scientist (ALX)
- Certified Foundation in Specialization in Digital Skills (ALX)
- Portfolio :- https://ebi-portfolio.vercel.app

REFEREES

Mr. Godswill Ikpotokin (Applinet Technologies) - 08093046050